Previously on Zombieland Saga Revenge!
A few months have passed since our epic fail at EFS,
and we're still not quite over it,
but it seems like a lot of good things are on the horizon for Pran Shushu!
Our Saga Arena concert filled our spirits,
and Lily landed a spot on a national TV talent show!
It's no surprise she made it to the finals,
but she was up against a child acting prodigy
who sang the same song Lily had planned!
Which is, like, the worst thing that could ever happen!
But Lily was such a genius that she improvised a scat arrangement
at the last minute!
It was so amazing that everyone was going
skibbity-ba-ba-ba-dee-ba-doo!
Wee-be-babble-bee-ba-wee-be-dee-babble-bee-
What's with the thousand-yard stare? A new story?
In a few years, you'll have the same look in your eyes.
Everyone has been talking about her online.
That girl looks exactly like Lily Hoshikawa.
They're also picking up on number three and four's likenesses.
After that radio show and Iron Frill calling them rivals,
they're trending like crazy.
Yeah, but most of the posts are jokes about the group
being a collection of doppelgangers.
The more famous you get, the more trolls start to come out.
You were the first one who made the connection
between number four and Junko Kono.
You should have started an expose that second.
I write the facts, not a gossip column.
The only theory I've heard the tracks is that their producer
is intentionally collecting look-alikes.
Wouldn't be surprised if the rest of them were look-alikes, too.
Hey, maybe he raised them from the dead like a bunch of zombies.
Take that trash talk to Mu, the occult mag.
Yes, sir, on my way right now.
Just kiddin'.
It's my lunch break.
As for the rest of them...
Hmmmm.
.